Irving P. Krick papers, 1921-1996
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Weather Modification Project
  - Miscellaneous weather maps (2 of 2) (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Eastern Canada (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Proposal: Australia (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Proposal: Australia (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Water Resources Development Corp, Colorado: General letters (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Trade List, Saudi Arabia - Business Firms (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Client reports: Comanche County Weather Modification Association Inc., Oklahoma (1 of 2) (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Client reports: Comanche County Weather Modification Association Inc., Oklahoma (2 of 2) (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Client reports: Cotton County Services Inc., Oklahoma (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Climatological data: Kansas (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Climatological data: Arkansas (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Climatological data: Oklahoma (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Climatological data: Louisiana (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Client reports: Hitch AGRI-Business Inc., Oklahoma (1 of 2) (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Client reports: Hitch AGRI-Business Inc., Oklahoma (2 of 2) (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Precipitation data: Texas (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Foreign prospect: Saudi Arabia (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Colorado River Water Users Association, California (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous weather data (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous articles (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Generator Operator's Manual, Silver Iodide Generator (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Forecast data, various U.S. cities (1 of 2) (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Forecast data, various U.S. cities (2 of 2) (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Forecast data, LEWIS, various U.S. cities (1 of 2) (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Forecast data, LEWIS, various U.S. cities (2 of 2) (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Ernst and Young, weekly forecasts (1 of 2) (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Ernst and Young, weekly forecasts (2 of 2) (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Weather data: Association of Distinguished American Scientists (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Weather estimates for Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - List of reports (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Forecast data, LEWIS, various U.S. cities (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Weather maps, Texas (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Weather maps, Texas (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Weather maps, Texas (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Weather maps, Texas (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Weather maps, Texas (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Weather maps, Texas (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Weather maps, Texas (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Daily summaries (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Daily summaries (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Daily summaries (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Daily summaries (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Daily summaries (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Daily summaries (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Daily summaries (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Tracings (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Tracings (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Tracings (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Tracings (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Tracings (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Atlantic and European Charts: Surface pressure and 500mb (Box 115)
  - Atlantic and European Charts: Surface pressure and 500mb (Box 116)
  - Atlantic and European Charts: Surface pressure and 500mb (Box 117)
  - Atlantic and European Charts: Surface pressure (Box 118)
  - Surface maps: France (Box 119)
  - European weather maps (Box 120)
  - European weather maps (Box 121)
  - Tracings: Weather charts (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Tracings: Weather charts (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Tracings: Weather charts (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Precipitation data: Oklahoma (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Client reports: State of Texas (1 of 2) (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Client reports: State of Texas (2 of 2) (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Precipitation data: New Mexico (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Precipitation data: Oklahoma (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Precipitation data: Oklahoma (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Rainfall in the Red Bluff Area, Forecast (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Crop forecasts, rought drafts: Various cities (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Local prospect: Oklahoma, clippings (1 of 3) (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Local prospect: Oklahoma, clippings (2 of 3) (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Local prospect: Oklahoma, clippings (3 of 3) (Box 123, Folder 8)